Finding Aid for University Planner's Office (University of Michigan) records, 1940-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Properties, 1850-2014
  - Buildings by number
    - 0886 Trotter house, 1977-2013
      - Digital records
    - 0890 Perry Building, 1965-2003 (Box 32)
    - 0897 1015 East Huron, 1976-2006 (Box 32)
    - 0948-0974 Radrick Farms, 1966-2006 (Box 32)
    - 0976-0994 Matthaei Botanical Gardens, 2010
      - Records, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Digital records
    - 1450-1453 McGraw Hill Observatory, 2003 (Box 32)
    - 1501 Rackham Education Memorial Detroit, 1943-2008 (Box 33)
    - 2201-2237 Willow Run 1961-2014
      - Records (Box 33)
      - Digital records
    - 2500 Mitchell Field, 1968-1986 (Box 33)
    - 2501-2504 Auxiliary Services, 1968-1982, 3 folders (Box 33)
    - 3401 Research Vessel Laurentian, 1998-2002 (Box 33)
    - 3410-3426 Peach Mountain Portage Lake Observatory and Stinchfield Woods, 1959-2004 (Box 33)
    - 3501-3511 Base Lake Farms Newcomb Tract, 1977-2002 (Box 33)
    - 3541 and 3542 Saginaw Forest and Buildings, 1953-2008 (Box 33)
    - 4001-4171 Biological Station, 1961-2009 (Box 33)
    - Records, 4 folders
      - Digital records
    - 4401-4418 E. S. Osborn Preserve, 1960-2002 (Box 33)
    - Campus Photographs and Negatives, undated (Box 33)
    - Outer Properties Slides, 1976-2002 (Box 33)
  - Buildings by name
    - Architectural Research Housing, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Architecture and Design Building, Reports
      - "Physical Condition and Reuse Feasibility Study of A & D Building" (Eberle M. Smith Associates), 1976 (Box 1)
      - Report on Planning and Development, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Argus Plant No. 2 (includes Michigan Media), 1980-1986 (Box 1)
    - Barbour Waterman Gymnasiums, 1950-1977 (Box 1)
    - Center for Research on Human Growth and Development, 1966-1967 (Box 1)
    - Child Care Center, 1970-1972 (Box 1)
    - Computing Center, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Continuation Center, Report, untitled, 1954 (Volume 1)
    - Economics Building, 1971-1982 (Box 1)
    - Engineering Technology Center, Water Resources Educational Facility, Report, Preliminary Plan (Swanson Associates), 1972 (Box 1)
    - Fresh Air Camp, 1962, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Furstenberg Student Study Center, Report, Phase II Report (William Kessler and Associates), 1972 (Box 1)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration, Proposed Project, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Great Lakes Fishery Laboratory, 1980-1983 (Box 1)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute, Reports
      - "A Biomechanical-Biomedical Addition to the Highway Safety Research Institute," 1967 (Box 1)
      - "Outline Specification and Schedule of Finishes" (Harley, Ellington, Cowin and Stirton), 1966 (Box 1)
    - Institute for Social Research, Report, Program Statement (Alden B. Dow Associates), undated (Box 1)
    - Midwest Water Pollution Laboratory and Bureau of Commercial Fisheries, 1962-1964 (Box 1)
    - Natural Science Building
      - General, 1972-1974 (Box 1)
      - Report, "E.H. Kraus Natural Science Building Survey Evaluation and Recommendations" (Colvin-Robinson Associates), undated (Box 1)
    - University Library, Reports
      - "Conceptual Studies, Renovation of General Library" (Albert Kahn Associates), 1969 (Box 1)
      - Preliminary Planning Documents (Albert Kahn Associates), 1972 (Box 1)
      - "Report for Albert Kahn, Evaluation of Roof Surfaces" (Construction Consultants), 1969 (Box 1)
      - "The University of Michigan Central Campus Library" (Albert Kahn Associates), 1964 (Box 1)
    - West Engineering
      - West Engineering Building, Report, "Historical Survey" (University Planner's Office), 1984 (Box 1)
      - West Engineering Building Survey, (Smith), 1984 (Box 1)
      - West Engineering (Koenig and Williams), undated (Box 1)
    - Wood Science and Technology Laboratory, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Removed Buildings
    - Index of Removed Buildings, undated (Box 34)
    - Campus Map of Removed Buildings, undated (Box 34)
    - R001-R003 Professor's Houses, undated (Box 34)
    - R006 Medical Building, 1850 (Box 34)
    - R007 Chemistry Building, 1856 (Box 34)
    - R008 First Law Building, 1863 (Box 34)
    - R009 Observatory Residence, 1869 (Box 34)
    - R010 West Hall, undated (Box 34)
    - R011 University Hall, 1872 (Box 34)
    - R012 Heating Plant, 1879 (Box 34)
    - R013 Hospital Residence, undated (Box 34)
    - R014 University Museum. 1880 (Box 34)
    - R015 General Library, 1883 (Box 34)
    - R016 Engineering Shops, 1885 (Box 34)
    - R017 Anatomical Lab, 1889 (Box 34)
    - R018 West Physics, 1889 (Box 34)
    - R019 University Hospital, 1891 (Box 34)
    - R020 First Laundry, 1891 (Box 34)
    - R023 Second Law Building, undated (Box 34)
    - R024 Waterman Gym, 1894 (Box 34)
    - R028 Nurses Home, 1899 (Box 34)
    - R033 Psychopathic Hospital, 1906 (Box 34)
    - R034 Dental Building, undated (Box 34)
    - R036 Eye and Ear Ward, 1909 (Box 34)
    - R037 Contagious Disease Hospital, 1914 (Box 34)
    - R038 Pigeon Left, 1914 (Box 34)
    - R039 Internes Home, undated (Box 34)
    - R040 Nurses Homes, undated (Box 34)
    - R041 University Hospital-Old Main, undated, 3 folders (Box 34)
    - R042 School of Music, undated (Box 35)
    - R043 Women's Athletic Building, 1928 (Box 35)
    - R045 Laundry, 1917 (Box 35)
    - R046 Dermatology Ward, 1918 (Box 35)
    - R049 1121 East Huron, 1920 (Box 35)
    - R050 Cheever House, 1921 (Box 35)
    - R051 Chemical Stores, 1921 (Box 35)
    - R052 Pemberton Welch Nurses Residence, 1921 (Box 35)
    - R053 University House 1921 (Box 35)
    - R054 East Hall, 1922 (Box 35)
    - R055 Geodesy and Surveying, 1907 (Box 35)
    - R056 Morris Hall, undated (Box 35)
    - R058 Hospital Animal House, 1924 (Box 35)
    - R059 Alumnae House, undated, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - R064 200, 202, 204, 206 South Forest, undated (Box 35)
    - R065 Storehouse Garage, 1928 (Box 35)
    - R066 Museums Animal House, 1929 (Box 35)
    - R067 X-Ray Storage, 1929 (Box 35)
    - R068 University Publications, undated (Box 35)
    - R069 Vertebrate Genetics Lab, 1931 (Box 35)
    - R070 Central Garage and Open Shed, 1934 (Box 35)
    - R071 Hospital Substation, 1934 (Box 35)
    - R072 University Storage Building, 1936 (Box 35)
    - R074 Substation, 1914 (Box 35)
    - R075 Boilerhouse, 1894 (Box 35)
    - R076 Automotive Lab, 1907 (Box 35)
    - R077 Children's Psychiatric Hospital, 1955 (Box 35)
    - R078 Alumnae House 1227 Washtenaw, undated (Box 35)
    - R079 Geddes House, undated (Box 35)
    - R081 Union Clubhouse, undated (Box 35)
    - R082 1102 East Ann, undated (Box 35)
    - R083 Fuller Street Warehouse and Storage, 1947 (Box 35)
    - R084 Temporary Classroom Building, 1947 (Box 35)
    - R087 Cheever House and Garage, 1948 (Box 35)
    - R088 Union Playhouse Mimes Theater, 1912 (Box 35)
    - R089 Quonset Huts, 1948 (Box 35)
    - R090 Wines Fields Buildings, undated (Box 35)
    - R092 School of Social Work, 1951 (Box 35)
    - R093 Metallurgical Research Building, 1950 (Box 35)
    - R094 ROTC Headquarters, undated (Box 35)
    - R085 Veterans Readjustment Center, 1947 (Box 35)
    - R086 Jefferson Apartments (Box 35)
    - R097 Sports Service Building, 1971 (Box 35)
    - R098 Research Activities Building, 1963 (Box 35)
    - R099 Architecture and Design Research Lab, 1955 (Box 35)
    - R100 733 South State, undated (Box 35)
    - R101 University Terrace Apartments, 1947 (Box 35)
    - R102 Mental Health Research Annex, undated (Box 35)
    - R103 Ferry Field Football Stadium, undated (Box 35)
    - R104 Tuberculosis Shacks, undated (Box 35)
    - R105 ROTC Temporary site, undated (Box 35)
    - R106 Latrines or Outhouse, undated (Box 35)
    - R107 Botanical Gardens on Packard, undated (Box 35)
    - R108 Reading and Learning Skills, undated (Box 35)
    - R109 Boilerhouse, 1884 (Box 35)
    - R110 Catholepistemiad, undated (Box 35)
    - R111 North University Building, undated (Box 35)
    - R112 Food Service Building, undated (Box 35)
    - R113 Veterans Housing near Gilsorn, undated (Box 35)
    - R114 Planada Apartments, undated (Box 35)
    - R115 Clinical Faculty Office Building, undated (Box 35)
    - R116 Houses, undated (Box 35)
    - R117 Corner House, undated (Box 35)
    - R118 721 South State, undated (Box 35)
    - R119 Riverview, undated (Box 35)
    - R120 Frieze Building, 1857-2006
      - Records, 3 folders (Box 35)
      - Digital records
    - R121 Assembly Hall, undated (Box 36)
    - R122 Paton Center, undated (Box 36)
    - R123 Business Administration, undated, 3 folders (Box 36)
    - R124 712 Oakland (Box 36)
    - R125 Kresge Medical Research Buildings I-III, 1955-2010 (Box 36)
    - R126 Kresge Hearing, 1960-2005 (Box 36)
    - R127 Upjohn Pharmacology, 1965-2004 (Box 36)
    - R128 Alice C. Lloyd Memorial Lab, 1986-2010 (Box 36)
    - R129 Towsley Center for Children, 1982-2008 (Box 36)
    - R130 Turner Geriatric, 1974-2012 (Box 36)
    - R131 Parkview Medical Center, 1961-2012 (Box 36)
    - R132 Law School Admissions, 1999-2013 (Box 36)
    - R134 South Ferry Field Sports Services Building, 2013 (Box 36)
    - R135 1021 East Huron, 2014 (Box 36)
    - R136 Computer and Executive Education Building, 1975-2014 (Box 36)
    - R137 Arbor Heights, 1946-2013 (Box 36)
    - Slides, 1971-2000, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous Properties
    - M001 Harris Hall, 1956 (Box 37)
    - M002 Kellogg-Warden House, 1989-1993 (Box 37)
    - M003 Toomy House (Box 37)
    - M004 Television Studio (Box 37)
    - M005 Kalmbach Management Center, 1983 (Box 37)
    - M006 Palmer Field (Box 37)
    - M007 Observatory at La Plata, undated (Box 37)
    - M008 Cat Hole-Palmer Drive Site, undated (Box 37)
    - M009 Lamont-Hussey Observatory, 2007 (Box 37)
    - M010 McMath-Hulbert Observatory, 1980-2004 (Box 37)
    - M011 Wall Street and Lower Town, 1995-2009, 1 folders (Box 37)
    - M012 Horner-McLaughlin Natural Area, 1973-2008 (Box 37)
    - M013 Harper Preserve, 1978-2008 (Box 37)
    - M014 Camp Filibert Roth, 2001 (Box 37)
    - M015 Botanical Gardens on Diag, undated (Box 37)
    - M016 Speech Camp, 1996 (Box 37)
    - M017 Keweenaw Rocket Launch Site, 1998-2002 (Box 37)
    - M018 Golf Course, 1929-2008
      - Records, 4 folders (Box 37)
      - Digital records
    - M019 Felch Park, 1966-1996 (Box 37)
    - M020 Missaukee County Preserve, 2003-2009 (Box 37)
    - M021 Mud Lake Boy Preserve, 2008 (Box 37)
    - M022 Ringwood Forest Preserve, 2008 (Box 37)
    - M023 Willow Run Airport and Willow Run Laboratory, 1965-2009 (Box 37)
    - M024 Gordon Hall, 1951-2005
      - Records, 9 folders (Box 38)
      - Digital records
    - National Register Gordon Hall 1972 (Box 38)
    - Property Costs, 1921-1946 (Box 38)
    - Property Expansion Study, 1944 (Box 38)
    - Appraisal Reports, 1922-1943 (Box 38)
  - Public Art
    - Art Acquisition-Grant Program, 1988-1990 (Box 39)
    - Art in Public Places, 1982-1998 (Box 39)
    - Detroit Art Registration and Information System, 1990 (Box 39)
    - North Campus Outdoor Sculpture Committee, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Dougherty Temporary Piece 1998 Bottles, 1998-1999 (Box 39)
    - Acacia Bench, 2002 (Box 39)
    - Flagpole-Central Campus 1918-2007 (Box 39)
    - Class of 1862-Rock, 2002-2005
      - Records (Box 39)
      - Digital records
    - Class of 1869 Rock and Plaque, 1997-2003 (Box 39)
    - Class of 1901 Bench, 2002 (Box 39)
    - Class of 1966 Block M, undated (Box 39)
    - Diag Block M, 2000-2013 (Box 39)
    - Sculpture Pieces ISR Convergence, 1989-2002 (Box 39)
    - Cube -- 1967 Rosenthal Sculpture, 1965-2009 (Box 39)
    - Daedalus, 1977-2009 (Box 39)
    - Doric Entry Portal, 1977-2007 (Box 39)
    - Athlete and Student, 1917-2000 (Box 39)
    - Friendship and Character, 1997 (Box 39)
    - Hamilton Fountain, 1997-2005 (Box 39)
    - Haven Elm Marker, 1997 (Box 39)
    - Holocaust Memorial, 1990-2004 (Box 39)
    - Social Work "Kindred", 2002-2003 (Box 39)
    - Lady of the Garden, 1997-2005 (Box 39)
    - LSA Façade Reliefs, 1997-2001 (Box 39)
    - Portia, 2003 (Box 39)
    - Professors Monument, 1997-2003 (Box 39)
    - Pumas, 2006, 2007
      - Records (Box 39)
      - Digital records
    - Rampant Unicorn, 1993-2006 (Box 39)
    - Science Benches, 1997-2005 (Box 39)
    - Spanish Mortar, 1996-1999 (Box 39)
    - Sunday Morning in Deep Waters, 1958-2006
      - Records (Box 40)
      - Digital records
    - Regeneration of Time, 1997-2005 (Box 40)
    - Rotations, 2009 (Box 40)
    - Two Boys and Dog, 1997-2001 (Box 40)
    - Tappan Oak and Marker, 1997-2000 (Box 40)
    - Tooth Fairy, 1997-2005 (Box 40)
    - Veltman Bust, 1997-2005 (Box 40)
    - Xi Psi Bench, 1997 (Box 40)
    - Dance Cylinder, 1979-2005 (Box 40)
    - Vessels, 2010 (Box 40)
    - Armillary, 2005-2011 (Box 40)
    - Begab, 1995-2005 (Box 40)
    - Bundle-Flickinger, 1997-2005 (Box 40)
    - Dream Plaques, 1994-2005 (Box 40)
    - Historical Circle and Peregrine Section, 1973-1997 (Box 40)
    - Richard Hunt, 1968-1988 (Box 40)
    - Hob Nob, 1979-2009 (Box 40)
    - Koszonom Raoul Wallenberg, 1994-2005 (Box 40)
    - Liberation, 2002 (Box 40)
    - Lorch Column, 1997-2009 (Box 40)
    - 1961-Onus, 1965-2005 (Box 40)
    - Relief Sculpture IV, 1997-2005 (Box 40)
    - SAI Sundial, 1971-2005 (Box 40)
    - Summaries of Arithmetic, 1991-2005 (Box 40)
    - Triad Ritual, 1993-2005 (Box 40)
    - Trio, 1997-2004 (Box 40)
    - Two Open Triangles, 1979-2005 (Box 40)
    - Wave Field, 1992-2003 (Box 40)
    - American Eagle, 1985-2005 (Box 40)
    - Wave Maker, 1997-2005 (Box 40)
    - Arbor Lakes Sculpture, 2002-2007 (Box 40)
    - Michigamua Emblem, 1967-2004 (Box 40)
    - Lost Pieces
      - Arch of Trajan, 1997 (Box 40)
      - Ben Franklin, 1997 (Box 40)
      - Figure of Michigan, 1999-2001 (Box 40)
      - Winged Victory of Samothrace, 2000 (Box 40)
    - Slides, 1973-1998, 2 folders (Box 40)
- Projects, 1950-2008
  The Projects series (1950-2008, 12.5 linear feet) generally concern issues that arise from the construction of a building or other campus development. These issues are broad-ranging and include parking lots and structures, changes in traffic patterns, exterior lighting, bicycle paths and bicycle racks, recreation areas, signage, pedestrian bridges and walkways, zoning issues, and landscaping. As the University Planner works in close contact with the University Architect, this record group also includes material concerning the numerous building projects on the three university campuses.
  - Ann Arbor, City of
    - General, 1966-1981 (Box 1)
    - Ann Arbor Blues Festival, 1970-1974 (Box 1)
    - Board of Education (re: Huron High School), 1962-1968 (Box 1)
    - Buffer Ordinance, Landscape and Land Use, 1968-1972 (Box 1)
    - Planning Department, 1960-1977 (Box 1)
    - Public Hearings on Zoning, 1964-1982 (Box 1)
    - R2B District, Zoning of, 1969-1974 (Box 1)
      (area of Hill St. and Washtenaw Ave. including fraternities, sororities and cooperative housing)
    - University-City Capital Projects for 1965-1970, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Urban Beautification, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Township, 1966, 1974, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Barr, Bradford (correspondence), 1964-1965 (Box 1)
  - Building Program (Ann Arbor Campus)
    - Capital Campaign (potential projects), 1975-1980 (Box 1)
    - Comprehensive Building Program, 1960-1970 (Box 1)
    - Physical Plant Development (Box 1)
      (includes copies of historical materials re: campus development dating to 1919)
    - Public Works Projects, 1976 (Box 1)
      (includes C.C. Little Building, S.T. Dana Building, Old Architecture and Design Building, University Hospital, Biological Station, Camp Filibert Roth, Engineering Building II)
    - Report, "The University of Michigan Classroom and Office Building Report on Planning and Development Part I," 1965 (Box 1)
  - Committees
    - Bicycle Discussion Group, 1979-1982 (Box 2)
    - Campus Planning Staff Committee
      - 1961/62-1972/73, 2 folders (Box 2)
      - 1975/76 (Box 2)
      - 1979/80 (Box 2)
    - Campus Sign Operations Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
    - Central Campus Parking Planning Committee, 1970 (Box 2)
    - City-University Coordinating Committee (formerly University-City Conference), 1960/61-1977/78, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Exterior Elements Design Review Committee
      (includes photographs)
      - 1967/68-1969/70 (Box 2)
      - 1973/74-1985/86, 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Exterior Lighting Committee, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Housing Committee, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Landscape Review Meetings, 1964/65-1967/68 (Box 2)
    - North Campus Operating Activities Committee, 1966-1973 (Box 2)
    - Northeast Area Planning Review Committee, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Northeast Campus Group, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Planning Data Steering Committee, University, 1966-1970 (Box 3)
    - SACUA Committee on Campus Planning and Development, 1961-1966 (Box 3)
    - South Central Campus Group, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
    - Faculty, Staff and Student Housing Issue, 1985-1990, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Fraternities
    - General, 1963-1970 (Box 4)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1966, 1968 (Box 4)
    - North Campus (proposed sites), 1961-1969
      - Fraternity Complex North Campus, 1968 (Box 41)
    - Nu Sigma Nu, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - Housing
    - General, 1965-1982 (Box 4)
    - Housing Sites, 1969-1975 (Box 4)
    - Housing Types
      - Mobile Homes, 1966, 1970, 1974 (Box 4)
      - Prefabricated Housing, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - Inter-Cooperative Council, 1965-1969
      - Inter-Cooperative Council Housing, 1987-1997 (Box 41)
    - Married Students
      - General, 1968-1973 (Box 4)
      - Northwood IV, 1966-1978 (includes photos) (Box 4)
      - Northwood V, 1968-1977 (Box 4)
    - Public Housing, 1968-1971
      - Public Housing Sites, 1962-1968 (Box 41)
    - Single Students
      - General, 1969-1977 (Box 4)
      - Baits, Vera, Houses (formerly Cedar Bend Houses), 1962-1967 (Box 4)
      - Bursley Hall, 1964-1967 (Box 4)
      - Potential Sites, 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Housing Feasibility Study, 1974 (Box 45)
      - Projects in Housing Study, 1974-1987 (Box 45)
    - Reports
      - "Northwoods I, II, & III Planning Study" (Office of the University Landscape Architect), 1985 (Box 4)
      - "Northwood V Specifications, Addendum No. 1" (G. Hellmuth and G. Obata, Architects), 1970 (Box 4)
      - "Program Development for Expansion of Affiliated-Associated Housing Facilities" (University Planner), 1968 (Box 4)
    - Housing Additional Student Study of Potential Sites, 1974-1995 (Box 42)
    - Housing History, 2008 (Box 45)
  - Huron River Valley Study/Huron River Recreation Resource Study, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - Interfaith Center, Inc., 1956-1968 (Box 4)
  - Loading Areas, 1968-1969, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Medical Center
    - General, 1950-1980, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Landscape Development, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Reports
      - Medical Center
        - "Building Conditions Study" (Eberle M. Smith Associates, Inc.), 1971, 3 volumes (Box 5)
        - "Medical Campus Library & Learning Resource Center, Life Cycle Study" (Hoyem-Basso Associates), 1977 (Box 5)
        - "University of Michigan Medical Center" (Skidmore, Owings & Merrill), 1950 (Box 5)
        - "1980 Projected Traffic Demands of the Medical Center" (Bradford Barr, Engineering Services), 1963 (Box 5)
      - University Hospital
        - "Functional and Space Program" (Coopers & Lybrand), 1978, 3 volumes (Box 5)
        - "Interim Renovations of Existing Operating Rooms, Diagnostic Radiology and Clinical Laboratory" (Harley Ellington Pierce Yee Associates), undated, 2 volumes (Box 6)
        - "Progress Report on Development of a Prospectus for the University of Michigan University Hospital" (Coopers & Lybrand), 1978 (Box 6)
        - "Reuse Reassignment Volume: Study of the University of Michigan Main Hospital" (Eberle M. Smith Associates), 1975 (Box 6)
  - North Campus
    - General, 1964-1978 (Box 6)
    - Schools, Elementary (proposed sites), 1963-1967, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Report, Program Statement, North Campus Commons Expansion (University Planner), 1986 (Box 6)
    - North Campus Report (Aaron Cohen Assoc.), 1986 (Box 6)
  - Pedestrians
    - General, 1964-1983 (Box 6)
    - Forest Avenue Pedestrian Bridge, 1966-1968 (Box 6)
    - Handicapped, 1969-1975 (Box 6)
  - Plant Department
    - Switching Station, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
    - Report, "Refuse Derived Fuel Facility for the University of Michigan" (Harley Ellington Pierce Yee Associates), 1982 (Box 6)
  - Recreation Areas
    - Intramural Sports Facilities, 1962-1981 (Box 6)
      (includes one b&w negative of 1969 "Intramural Recreation Facilities" blueprint)
    - Northwood I, II & III, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Northwood IV, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Northwood V, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Saint Joseph Mercy Hospital, Old (North Ingalls Building)
    - General, 1965-1979 (Box 6)
      (includes 5 b&w contact sheets, 1969)
    - Reports
      - "Preliminary Inventory and Evaluation: Saint Joseph Hospital Property" (University Planner's Office), 1969 (Box 6)
        (includes photographs and slides)
      - "The University of Michigan Building Condition Study for St. Joseph Mercy Hospital" (Eberle M. Smith Associates), 1974 (Box 6)
  - Service Centers
    - General, 1962-1969 (Box 6)
    - Report, "CSC North Campus: A Study of Program Development." 1965 (Box 6)
      (re: proposed Commercial and Service Center) (First Year Graduate Students, Dept. of Landscape Architecture)
  - North Campus Landscape Competition, 1995 (Box 43)
  - Signs, Interior and Exterior
    - General, 1966-1974 (Box 7)
      (includes 11 color photos of exterior campus signs)
    - Medical Center Signage Study
      - General, 1978 (Box 7)
      - Report, "Interior Signage Manual, University Hospital" (Smith, Hinchman & Grylls Associates), undated (Box 7)
  - Student Projects, 1964-1967 (Box 7)
    (generally re: campus planning or landscape architecture)
  - Traffic, Transportation and Parking
    - Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Urban Area Transportation Study
      - General, 1964-1978 (Box 7)
      - Technical Committee and M-17 Subcommittee, 1970-1972 (Box 7)
    - Bicycles and Motorcycles, 1964-1970 (Box 7)
    - Bus Service
      - Ann Arbor, 1973-1976 (Box 7)
      - Campus, 1965-1978 (Box 7)
    - Car Pools, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Crisler Arena/University Events Building, 1964, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Dearborn Campus, 1964-1981 (Box 7)
    - Jefferson Plaza Traffic Analysis, 1964 (Box 7)
    - Mass Transportation, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
    - Medical Center Area, 1957-1987, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - North Campus, 1964-1980 (Box 7)
    - Origin and Destination Traffic Survey (North Central Campus and State Street)
      - General, 1963-1967 (Box 7)
      - Reports
        - "North Central Campus-State Street Origin and Destination Traffic Survey," 1966 (Box 7)
        - "Technical Supplement," 1966 (Box 7)
    - Parking and Parking Structures
      - General, 1963-1981 (Box 7)
      - Catherine Street Structure, 1964, 1985 (Box 7)
      - Church Street Structure, 1964, 1966, 1971 (Box 7)
      - Compact Cars, 1968-1985 (Box 7)
      - Fletcher Street Structure, 1958-1976 (Box 7)
      - Forest Street Structure, 1976 (Box 7)
      - Hill Street Structure, 1964-1969 (Box 7)
      - Parking Meters, 1970-1983 (Box 7)
      - Parking Space Data (annual tabulations), 1963-1977 (Box 8)
      - Thayer Street Structure, 1964-1965 (Box 8)
      - Thompson Street Structure, 1969-1975 (Box 8)
      - Parking Structure Site Study, 1958 (Box 41)
      - Central Campus Parking Study, 1989 (Box 42)
      - Air Contaminants in Parking Structures, 1964 (Box 43)
      - Expanded Parking Paradigm Study, 1994-1996 (Box 44)
    - Streets and Intersections
      - General, 1964-1980 (Box 8)
      - East University Street, 1966-1970 (Box 8)